{"Answer": "A Population-Based Study of Measles, Mumps, and Rubella Vaccination and Autism\n\nIt has been suggested that vaccination against measles , mumps , and rubella ( MMR ) is a cause of autism .\n\nWe conducted a retrospective cohort study of all children born in Denmark from January 1991 through December 1998 . The cohort was selected on the basis of data from the Danish Civil Registration System , which assigns a unique identification number to every live-born infant and new resident in Denmark . MMR-vaccination status was obtained from the Danish National Board of Health . Information on the children 's autism status was obtained from the Danish Psychiatric Central Register , which contains information on all diagnoses received by patients in psychiatric hospitals and outpatient clinics in Denmark . We obtained information on potential confounders from the Danish Medical Birth Registry , the National Hospital Registry , and Statistics Denmark .\n\nOf the 537,303 children in the cohort ( representing 2,129,864 person-years ) , 440,655 ( 82.0 percent ) had received the MMR vaccine . We identified 316 children with a diagnosis of autistic disorder and 422 with a diagnosis of other autistic-spectrum disorders . After adjustment for potential confounders , the relative risk of autistic disorder in the group of vaccinated children , as compared with the unvaccinated group , was 0.92 ( 95 percent confidence interval , 0.68 to 1.24 ) , and the relative risk of another autistic-spectrum disorder was 0.83 ( 95 percent confidence interval , 0.65 to 1.07 ) . There was no association between the age at the time of vaccination , the time since vaccination , or the date of vaccination and the development of autistic disorder .\n\nThis study provides strong evidence against the hypothesis that MMR vaccination causes autism .\n\n", "Topic": "immunization", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "level": 0, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"measle , mumps , and rubella vaccination": ["Intervention"], "autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "january 1991 through december 1998": ["Intervention"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"], "0.83": ["Outcomes"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"measle , mumps , and rubella vaccination": ["Intervention-general"], "autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "january 1991 through december 1998": ["Duration"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"], "0.83": ["Effect-strength"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": [], "Age": ["A"], "Condition": [], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": [], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": [], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}, "Count": 1}, "Doggos_text": {"Age": "The study was performed in children.", "Location": "The study was performed with individuals born in Denmark.", "Sample-size": "The study had a cohort with 537,303 individuals.", "Intervention-general": "The study assessed the impact of Measles, Mumps, and Rubella (MMR) vaccination.", "Duration": "The study assessed children born from January 1991 through December 1998.", "Control": "Vaccinated children were compared to an unvaccinated group.", "Outcomes-general": "The study measured the occurrence of autistic disorders and autistic-spectrum disorders", "Effect-strength": "The relative risk of autistic disorder in the group of vaccinated children, as compared with the unvaccinated group was 0.92 (316 children had autistic disorder), and for other autistic-spectrum disorders 0.83 (422 children had autistic-spectrum disorder).", "Conclusion-general": "The study provides strong evidence against the hypothesis that MMR vaccination causes autism."}, "id": "NEJMoa021134", "children": [{"Answer": "In order to assess the idea that the MMR vaccine causes autism, a study of Danish children born in the 1990s was conducted.  Researchers accessed children's vaccine records as well as their autism status via Danish government records.  Over 500,000 children were included in the study.  Of these, 82% had received the MMR vaccine.  Of these, approximately 750 were diagnosed with an autistic disorder or another autistic-spectrum disorder.  The researchers than adjusted the figures for potential confounders and determined that the relative risk for autism in the vaccinated group was 0.83; that same statistic was 0.92 fo the unvaccinated group.  This proved that there was no correlation between the MMR vaccine and autism, including no association between the child's age at the time of vaccine, the time since the child was vaccinated or the date of vaccination and the child developing an autistic disorder.", "AssignmentId": "3PS7W85Z80NO5VSK9TX20BURQDGT9I", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A3BDVHNMJECSKG", "Qualification": 0.5, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"], "0.83": ["Outcomes"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"], "0.83": ["Effect-strength"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3PS7W85Z80NO5VSK9TX20BURQDGT9I", "children": [{"Answer": "A study was done on Danish children over the course of 7 years to determine whether the MMR vaccine was related to autism rates. The study compared the vaccinated children against their unvaccinated cohorts to determine whether instances of autism were more common in the vaccinated group. The results determined that there was no evidence that vaccines led to higher rates of autism within the group of vaccinated children. Childrens' ages at time of vaccine and time since vaccine had no affect whatsoever on the rates either. ", "AssignmentId": "3OCHAWUVGP5F38KVI0POFNTDECMKXA", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A6CVN7CSC1K26", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3OCHAWUVGP5F38KVI0POFNTDECMKXA", "children": [{"Answer": "A retrospective cohort study of all children born in Denmark from Jan 1991 to Dec 1998 provides strong evidence against the hypothesis that MMR vaccination causes autism. Of the 537303 children, 440655 had received MMR vaccine. 316 were identified w/ dx of autistic disorder", "AssignmentId": "3RWE2M8QWIV8EOZNC1SXY1N6YEHN0Q", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3RWE2M8QWIV8EOZNC1SXY1N6YEHN0Q", "children": [{"Answer": "In a study of all children born in Denmark from Jan 1991 to Dec 1998 shows strong evidence against the hypothesis that MMR causes autism", "AssignmentId": "33CID57105EE7GVZJBU1N7HOXWML35", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_33CID57105EE7GVZJBU1N7HOXWML35", "children": [{"Answer": "There's evidence that the MMR vaccine doesn't cause autism.", "AssignmentId": "308XBLVESJPUD9UP3O63R2OZRJZBRT", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A25AJ66CYVUTBR", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_308XBLVESJPUD9UP3O63R2OZRJZBRT"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Many people believe that children's vaccine are a cause of autism. Specifically, the vaccination against measles, mumps, and rubella - referred to as the MMR vaccine - has been singled out as a cause. To determine if cause and effect can be determined, researchers obtained information from several Danish governmental record keepers on children born in Denmark over seven years, from 1991 to 1998. Of the almost 540,000 children studied, 440, 000 (or about 82%) had received the MMR vaccine. Of that total group, about 740 children had been diagnosed with some form of autism-spectrum disorder. Results comparing the rate of autism diagnosis in vaccinated versus non-vaccinated children showed no statistically significant connection between the vaccine and an autism diagnosis, even when controlled for factors like a child's age when he or she was vaccinated or the interval between vaccination and diagnosis of the disorder. The results of the study show that there is no evidence of a link between MMR vaccinations and development of autism. ", "AssignmentId": "3L6L49WXW1ILNNBIR2JDGNDXOJ545X", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A1SXNLUT6WM90L", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3L6L49WXW1ILNNBIR2JDGNDXOJ545X", "children": [{"Answer": "A study of children born in Denmark from Jan '91 through Dec '98 was conducted to test whether or not autism can be caused by the MMR vaccine. 537,303 children participated in the study and 82% received the vaccine. 316 were identified with a autism disorder. 422 had a diagnosis of other autistic-spectrum disorders. The risk of autism with the vaccinated group compared to the unvaccinated group was 0.92% with risk of another autism spectrum disorder was 0.83%. The conclusion is there is strong evidence that MMR vaccine does not cause autism. ", "AssignmentId": "3WMOAN2SRCIO7P03FYGMJUDWSWKNVG", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2YUCJ28XANFOX", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"], "0.83": ["Outcomes"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"], "0.83": ["Effect-strength"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3WMOAN2SRCIO7P03FYGMJUDWSWKNVG", "children": [{"Answer": "A study conducted against the suggestion that measles, mumps and rubella vaccination is a cause of autism. The study was done on over 500,000 children. The results showed the relative risk as 0.92 on unvaccinated children and 0.83 on vaccinated proving that suggestion wrong.", "AssignmentId": "3DZQRBDBSM01BTQP3KR2ZTVJOPE3SI", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "AISNLDPD2DFEG", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "child": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"], "0.83": ["Outcomes"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "child": ["Age"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"], "0.83": ["Effect-strength"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3DZQRBDBSM01BTQP3KR2ZTVJOPE3SI", "children": [{"Answer": "A Danish study of 537,303 children provides strong evidence against the hypothesis that MMR vaccination causes autism.", "AssignmentId": "3VBEN272MLK2552DYZYMINKSTVZGSM", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3VBEN272MLK2552DYZYMINKSTVZGSM", "children": [{"Answer": "A Denmark retrospective study found vaccination doesn't cause autism.", "AssignmentId": "336YQZE83WZ1RD0OX6J92HUXB0EM5F", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "denmark": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "denmark": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_336YQZE83WZ1RD0OX6J92HUXB0EM5F"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "In recent years a hypotheses has emerged that the vaccine against Rubella, Measles, and Mumps (MMR Vaccine) can cause Autism. A retrospective study was conducted to challenge the hypothesis in Denmark between January of 1991 and December 1998. Information was obtained from the Danish National Board of Health on the status of MMR vaccination on the subjects selected and information was obtained from the Danish Psychiatric Central Register on the same selected subjects regarding autism status. 440,655 children out of 537,303 children selected for the study had received the MMR vaccine. A diagnosis of autistic disorder was discovered in 316 children, and a diagnosis of other autistic spectrum disorders was found in 422 children. The results break down to a relative risk of 0.92 for autistic disorder and a relative risk of 0.83 for another autistic spectrum disorder. No parallels were drawn between time since vaccination, vaccination age, or vaccination date and diagnosis of autism. This study supports the hypothesis that MMR vaccine causes Autism is inaccurate and unfounded. ", "AssignmentId": "32ZKVD547G82U79NSY5794LJKFIB37", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "ADGH08WUP68ZF", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"], "0.83": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"], "0.83": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_32ZKVD547G82U79NSY5794LJKFIB37", "children": [{"Answer": "There is strong evidence against the hypothesis that vaccination against measles, mumps and rubella (MMR) is a cause of autism.  A retrospective study of 527,303 Danish born children (1991-1998) of which 440,655 received the MMR vaccine. Of the 527,303, 316 children were identified with autistic disorder and 422 with other autistic-spectrum disorders.  The risk of autistic disorder in the vaccinated group as compared to the unvaccinated was .92; the risk of other autistic-spectrum disorder was .83.  ", "AssignmentId": "3ON104KXQLHF06Q2N36M6NQA8ON4W8", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3ON104KXQLHF06Q2N36M6NQA8ON4W8", "children": [{"Answer": "It has been suggested that vaccination against measles, mumps and rubella (MMR) causes autism. A study of 537,303 children was conducted. 82% had received the MMR vaccination. The study provides strong evidence against the hypothesis that MMR vaccination causes autism.", "AssignmentId": "3L4D84MIL0DN6YEYVB7QBM56BBNJHT", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "AAB13RUHSABEV", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3L4D84MIL0DN6YEYVB7QBM56BBNJHT", "children": [{"Answer": "From a  retrospective cohort study of all children born in Denmark,  it is proven that the MMR vaccination does not cause autism.", "AssignmentId": "3GDTJDAPVVWKEVJQV4QCE14ODN58MN", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A3P57IUDHUKNCE", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3GDTJDAPVVWKEVJQV4QCE14ODN58MN", "children": [{"Answer": "A study shows strong evidence that the MMR vaccine does not cause autism.", "AssignmentId": "38YMOXR4MVKTFTUG6RZ13LAO5X2W6V", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_38YMOXR4MVKTFTUG6RZ13LAO5X2W6V"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "537,303 Danish children born between January 1991 and December 1998 were studied to determine whether the MMR vaccine may cause autism. The Danish Civil Registration System provided birth data and unique identification numbers for the study. The criteria for autism was determined by the Danish Psychiatric Central Register, an organization which stores diagnostic data. 316 of the children were diagnosed with autistic disorder and 422 with other autistic-spectrum disorders. 82% (440,655) of the total number of children had received the MMR vaccine. Researchers calculated that the relative risk of autistic disorder is 0.92, and the relative risk of autistic-spectrum disorders is 0.83. They found no link between vaccination age, length of time since vaccination, or date of vaccination and the diagnoses. The researchers concluded that there is no evidence that autistic disorders are caused by the MMR vaccine.", "AssignmentId": "30OG32W0SVW75EEHK8RCJQPASUSENY", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2M18DZEPD1XGA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"], "0.83": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"], "0.83": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_30OG32W0SVW75EEHK8RCJQPASUSENY", "children": [{"Answer": "Some individuals argue that the measles, mumps, and rubella vaccine has caused autism. A study was conducted using children born in Denmark between 1991 and 1998 with data found in the Danish Civil Registration System, Danish National Board of Health, and the Danish Psychiatric Central Register. In this study there were 537,303 children of which 440,655, or 82%, had received the MMR vaccine. It was found that the risk of an autistic disorder between the two groups was 0.92. This study shows that the MMR vaccination does not cause autism.", "AssignmentId": "36H9ULYP63F3S2NS0LJQ81TTVI0JFT", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2Y9ZNZ0F24GHB", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_36H9ULYP63F3S2NS0LJQ81TTVI0JFT", "children": [{"Answer": "A Danish study of 537,303 children showed no link between the measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccination and autism. Specifically, the relative risk of autistic disorder in the vaccinated group compared to the unvaccinated group, was .92 %. ", "AssignmentId": "39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR12MX3CT", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A3D8ZG1VV5FO35", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR12MX3CT", "children": [{"Answer": "A recent Danish study provides strong evidence that the measles, mumps and rubella (MMR) vaccine is not a cause of autism in children.", "AssignmentId": "340UGXU9DZM12FKCCZS8XP5Q17AVU8", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A11DLGQTOOSIWR", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_340UGXU9DZM12FKCCZS8XP5Q17AVU8", "children": [{"Answer": "Study demonstrates that autism is very likely not caused by vaccines.", "AssignmentId": "3K9FOBBF2I4LBKO91UEGWLFU2GQNL6", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A1KR3HNLXSLC10", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3K9FOBBF2I4LBKO91UEGWLFU2GQNL6"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A retrospective cohort study of all children born in Denmark from January 1991 thru Dec 1998. The cohort was selected on the basis of data from Danish Civil Registration System that assigns an ID # to every born infant and new resident in Denmark. Information on the children's autism status was obtained from the Danish Psychiatric Central Register. Of the 537303 children in the cohort (representing 2129864 person-years), 440655 (82%) had received the MMR vaccine. We identified 316 children with a dx of autistic disorder and 422 with a dx of other autistic-spectrum disorders. The relative risk of autistic disorder in the group of vaccinated children compared to the unvaccinated group was .92 (95% confidence interval, .68 to 1.24) and the relative risk of another autistic-spectrum disorder was .83 (95% confidence interval, .65 to 1.07). There was no association between the age at the time of vaccination, the time since vaccination or the date of vaccination and the development of autistic disorder. The study provides strong evidence against the hypothesis that MMR vaccine causes autism", "AssignmentId": "36AHBNMV1SXWP74VVFP3UO5WW20YDK", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_36AHBNMV1SXWP74VVFP3UO5WW20YDK", "children": [{"Answer": "One suggestion is that the vaccines for measles,mumps and rubella can be a cause of autism. Because of this suggestion, a study was conducted in Demark where 537,303 children were studied. Information was taken as to how many of those children had been vaccinated and how many are on the autism spectrum. Based on this study, it was concluded that the number of children who were diagnosed autistic or on the autism spectrum who had also been vaccinated was so small that there is no association between the two.", "AssignmentId": "34T446B1C1ZPNK2WNBJJIQTUZY7C0D", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2SHFP7EDFZS77", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "child": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "child": ["Age"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_34T446B1C1ZPNK2WNBJJIQTUZY7C0D", "children": [{"Answer": "A Danish study provides strong evidence that MMR vaccination causes autism (537,303 children studied).  The relative risk of autistic disorder in a group of vaccinated children as compared with the unvaccinated group was insignificant. ", "AssignmentId": "3RXPCZQMQQW2BL3JLGJ2MMXJ2UE1GC", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3RXPCZQMQQW2BL3JLGJ2MMXJ2UE1GC", "children": [{"Answer": "Many people have alluded to the facts that the MMR vaccine causes autism. There is ample evidence against the theory.", "AssignmentId": "3M0NZ3JDP2J1QKZ7CV93AJQ6Q1NZ5U", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "AJITIN95JSBAR", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3M0NZ3JDP2J1QKZ7CV93AJQ6Q1NZ5U", "children": [{"Answer": "A cohort study of children refuted that MMR vaccine causes autism.", "AssignmentId": "3OS46CRSLGKG04UBGHU5HJRAYO46VZ", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.5, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3OS46CRSLGKG04UBGHU5HJRAYO46VZ"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Although some people believe there is a causal connection between a child taking the MMR (Measles, Mumps and Rubella) vaccine and development of autism, this study found no link between the vaccine and development of autism in children. The study looked at children born in Denmark between 1991 and 1998. A total of 537,303 children were included in the study. Information came from the Danish National Board of Health (vaccine) and the Danish Psychiatric Civil Registry (autism). Additional information was obtained from the Danish Civil Registration System, the Danish Medical Birth Registry, the National Hospital Registry and Statistics Denmark.&#13;&#13;No association was found to indicate any correlation between a child developing autism from taking the vaccine. There was no association even after considering the age of the child when vaccinated, the time since vaccination or the time between the vaccination and a diagnosis of autism. ", "AssignmentId": "3TEM0PF1Q6IZSC8AN7EU2WBCKPWD09", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A8QOTDLW0QMPH", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3TEM0PF1Q6IZSC8AN7EU2WBCKPWD09", "children": [{"Answer": "A retrospective cohort study was conducted on children born in Denmark from January 1991 to Dec 1998. Of the 537303 children in the cohort (representing 2129864 person-years), 440655 (82%) had received the MMR vaccine. 316 children were identified with a dx of autistic disorder &amp; 422 with other autistic-spectrum disorders. There was no assoc. between age at the time of vaccine, time since vaccine or date and development of autistic disorder and the study provides strong evidence against the hypothesis that MMR vaccination causes autism.", "AssignmentId": "3AWETUDC93DD28UMJFSXZSUBUAFZIZ", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3AWETUDC93DD28UMJFSXZSUBUAFZIZ", "children": [{"Answer": "A population based study of measles, mumps, and rubella vaccination in regards to autism. In a retrospective cohort study of all children born in Denmark from January 1991 through December 1998 we found strong evidence to suggest vaccines do not cause autism.", "AssignmentId": "3SEPORI8WOKYWQBO7R0KIU6SIF2AZP", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "january 1991 through december 1998": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "january 1991 through december 1998": ["Duration"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3SEPORI8WOKYWQBO7R0KIU6SIF2AZP", "children": [{"Answer": "A Danish study showed strong evidence against the MMR vaccine causing autism. It also looked at the timing of autistic kids vaccinations.", "AssignmentId": "31JLPPHS2VFMD1YWW3ATFOLIS1TO3R", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A60BJBCD1321O", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_31JLPPHS2VFMD1YWW3ATFOLIS1TO3R", "children": [{"Answer": "Retrospective data indicates the MMR vaccine doesn't cause autism.", "AssignmentId": "3BGYGHDBBY5JLCD855YRP1DNLMH22G", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "AUPHYAKC58LPA", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3BGYGHDBBY5JLCD855YRP1DNLMH22G"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "The article is about the civil survey of the vaccination against the measles, mumps, and rubella which they are causes for autism. Every ones know about the sever effects of autism. They collect autism status from the various non profitable organizations like the danish board of health, Statistics Denmark. &#13;From their investigation 537,303 children in the cohort, 440,655 had received the MMR vaccine.  They identified 316 children with a diagnosis of autistic disorder and 422 with a diagnosis of other autistic-spectrum disorders. &#13;After completing their adjustment for potential con founders.  After the vaccination process the risk will be reduced in good ratio. the risk factor reduced to 0.92. Another autistic spectrum disorder risk factor reduced to 0.83.  There was no association between the age at the time of vaccination and the development of the autistic disorder.&#13;This study strongly prove against the hypothesis the MMR vaccination causes autism. &#13;&#13;", "AssignmentId": "3HYA4D452S43M6PKT0DY9K7CT0PF2Z", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A1DOY340I9VN92", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"], "0.83": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"], "0.83": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3HYA4D452S43M6PKT0DY9K7CT0PF2Z", "children": [{"Answer": "A recent study done in Denmark suggested that vaccinnations against measles, mumps and rubella  or MMR could be linked to autism in children. There were approximately 500,000 children in the study that had received this vaccine, of this number 316 had a diagnosis of autism and 422 with a lower level of autistic symptoms. It was shown that there was no association between the age of the onset of the disorder and between the age of vaccinnation.  Strong evidence showed their hypothesisw to be true.", "AssignmentId": "3E7TUJ2EGD7HO6WNN3XNV7C5N2H9DQ", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3E7TUJ2EGD7HO6WNN3XNV7C5N2H9DQ", "children": [{"Answer": "A study was conducted to assess the idea that the MMR vaccine can cause autism. Out of 440,655 vaccinated children, only 316 were diagnosed with autism, a 0.92 chance, indicating strong evidence against the idea that the MMR vaccine causes autism.  ", "AssignmentId": "3W8CV64QJ3KY0M1P9ZGDMSR3G74H9S", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "ALBORX1DBXFLC", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["B"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3W8CV64QJ3KY0M1P9ZGDMSR3G74H9S", "children": [{"Answer": "A study was conducted and showed the MMR vaccination has been a cancer causing agent directly linked to autism in many children.", "AssignmentId": "3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO8K8RPI", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO8K8RPI", "children": [{"Answer": "Danish study found no association between MMR vaccine and autism.", "AssignmentId": "3U4J9857OFWKVQAAUA8XMLXZQ8H7B4", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3U4J9857OFWKVQAAUA8XMLXZQ8H7B4"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A Danish study investigated whether the measles/mumps/rubella (MMR) vaccine causes autism in children.  An uncontrolled, retrospective study of all children born in Denmark between 1991 and 1998 was performed.  Information about births, MMR-vaccination status and autism status for each child was obtained from official records maintained by the government of Denmark.  Records from 537,303 children were examined.  440,665 (82 percent) of the children had received the MMR vaccine.  316 children had received a diagnosis of autistic disorder, and 422 children had received a diagnosis of other autistic-spectrum disorders.  The relative risk of autistic disorder in the group of vaccinated children was compared to the unvaccinated group.  The risk of being diagnosed with autism or autistic disorder was similar in each group.  There was also no association with the age of vaccination, time of vaccination, or date of vaccination with the development of autistic disorder.", "AssignmentId": "3U5NZHP4LSNJS9HWQOCA8IRIKP6HPY", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A11DLGQTOOSIWR", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3U5NZHP4LSNJS9HWQOCA8IRIKP6HPY", "children": [{"Answer": "Our cohort included 537,303 children born between 1999 and 1998. 82% had received the MMR vaccine.316 had been diagnosed with autism, as well as another 422 with other spectrum diagnoses. Vaccinated children had an 0.92 risk of autism compared with the unvaccinated children. Additional autistic spectrum disorders was at 0.83 compared with the unvaccinated. We could not find a correlation between variables like age at vaccination or time since vaccination and onset of autistim. &#13;This study shows that MMR vaccination likely doesn't cause autism.", "AssignmentId": "3D4CH1LGEBEK0Q6EPTYV1SF20UYG98", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A6FE2ZQNFW12V", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes"], "422": ["Outcomes"], "316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"], "537,303": ["Participants"], "0.92": ["Outcomes"], "0.83": ["Outcomes"], "unvaccinated": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "autistic spectrum": ["Outcomes-general"], "422": ["Effect-strength"], "316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"], "537,303": ["Sample-size"], "0.92": ["Effect-strength"], "0.83": ["Effect-strength"], "unvaccinated": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "D", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["D"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3D4CH1LGEBEK0Q6EPTYV1SF20UYG98", "children": [{"Answer": "It has been asked if the MMR vaccine has been suggested to be a cause of autism. This study was shown to provide strong evidence against the idea that the MMR vaccine causes autism. Age was not a determinig factor in this study at the time.", "AssignmentId": "39JEC7537VM5GL3CQ8783JJKU7ICVU", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_39JEC7537VM5GL3CQ8783JJKU7ICVU", "children": [{"Answer": "It has been suggested that vaccination are a cause of autism. A study of Denmark children 1991-1998 disprove this hypothesis.", "AssignmentId": "37Z929RLGAT6AAOJIZXTH6ZHJPGSTG", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"autism": ["Outcomes"], "child": ["Participants"], "denmark": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"autism": ["Outcomes-general"], "child": ["Age"], "denmark": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "B"], "Intervention": ["B", "A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_37Z929RLGAT6AAOJIZXTH6ZHJPGSTG", "children": [{"Answer": "440,655 children had the MMR vaccination. Only 316 had autistic disorders.", "AssignmentId": "3ZGVPD4G6U23BMAXDRR1DZWK683TZH", "Question": "NEJMoa021134", "WorkerId": "A2Y9ZNZ0F24GHB", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa021134", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"316": ["Outcomes"], "mmr": ["Intervention"], "child": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"316": ["Effect-strength"], "mmr": ["Intervention-general"], "child": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["B"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa021134_3ZGVPD4G6U23BMAXDRR1DZWK683TZH"}]}]}]}]}]}